Hvað er það?
On a cross and were buried in a grave, laid there by mortals you have made, though by
your word had the universe been created.
Therefore, when you shackled the enemy,
wandering his kingdom and spirit,
boiling him.
Down in Hades,
everyone cried out to you
as they saw your life,
life bringing rising.
Christ is risen,
who is forever,
the giver of life everlasting.
Both now and forever into the ages of ages of men.
Come believers, let us see where Christ the Savior has been born.
Let us follow where the star guides us with magi from the east.
Then choirs of angels unceasingly sing their praises.
Shepherds of the Lord
and their flocks in the fields abide,
offering them praise and upfitting hymn,
singing the anthem, glory in the highest
to the one born in a cave to death.
From her, the mother of God,
on her
In Bethlehem of Trudelion.
You rose the immortal one out of the grave as true God.
You raised with you the universe by your return from the dead.
O Christ, our deliverer, triumphing by your power over Hades' dominion,
showing your great compassion for all things by your rising.
Therefore, we worship you, alone are the friend of man.
Amen.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
and
the
Oh
He'll give you hope.
Both now and ever into the ages of ages.
Amen.
Mary, why are you amazed at what is taking place in you?
Because I gave birth in time to an eternal son, she says.
but I do
do not understand how he was conceived in me.
I have not known man, how then can I bear a son
who has ever seen birth without man see?
But as it is written, where God so wills,
the order of
all
nature is overcome
for Christ is born
from the blessed
virgin in Bethlehem
of Judea
Oh
O Lord, teach me your truths.
Why do you mingle sweet spices with your tears, O women disciples?
that
The wrestling angel in the tomb said to the myrrh-bearing women,
Behold the tomb and under the Savior has risen from the grave.
O Lord, teach me your statutes.
Lama
Bearing women, coming with spices to your grateful Savior.
Heard an angel saying to them, Why do you number living with the dead?
For as good he has risen from the dead.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Both now and forever, until the ages of ages, amen.
By giving birth to the giver of life, you redeemed Adam from sin, O virgin.
and you brought deep joy instead of sorrow.
He who was incarnate from you.
who is both God and man, has guided back to life
those who have fallen from life.
Alleluia, alleluia, alleluia,
alleluia, alleluia, alleluia,
Glory to you, O God.
Alleluia, alleluia, alleluia,
Lord, shall see you at all.
Alleluia, alleluia.
And yet, yet, we shall pray through.
Lord, have mercy.
Oh
and protect us, O God, by your grace.
Remembering our most holy, immaculate, most blessed and glorious Lady,
the Theotokos and our Virgin Mary, with all the saints,
let us command ourselves and one another and our whole life to Christ our God.
For blessed is your name and glorified is your kingdom of the Father,
I don't know.
Son and Holy Spirit, now and forever and to the ages of ages.
Amen.
The murder is proclaimed to the apostles,
the news of your wondrous rise and your prize,
that as God you have risen, granting the world your great mercy.
.
Oh, you hate Zion.
May you be put to shame by the Lord,
or you will be dried up as grass by fire.
Thank you.
Divine ears are given even to me.
I'm the Lord of the Lord of the Lord.
Martin, Megan, Brian, children.
Glory to the Father, into the Son, into the Holy Spirit,
and the Lord of the Lord.
by the warning
the streams of grace well water water being all creation to engender life
As one who has tendered love for my
the
of ages, amen.
By the Holy Spirit
comes wealth and
divine knowledge,
contemplation and
wisdom, for by him
the word of
the father's teaching
arise lord help us and redeem us
for the glory of your name.
this is
this
james
James, Sarah Lee.
Ση Κύριε Αναγία
το Πατρί και το Υιό και το Υιό Πνεύμα την οικία και εις τους αιώνας των αιώνων.
Αμήν.
Ο Σωτήρ και Βυστισμού από το τάφος,
ο Θεός ανέστησε εκ των θεσμών τους
η γενής και πύλας άγους συνέθλιψε
και ο Θεσπούτησαν έστη τριμερός.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Let all of us who are born on earth sing the praise of Christ, the giver of life,
who rose from the dead on the third day from the tomb,
and by his power today smashed the gates of death,
put Hades to death, and crushed the sting of death,
set Adam free with Eve, as with thanksgiving we cry aloud our fervent praise,
for he is alone the mighty God,
and Master rose on the third day.
I'm a composer, Peter.
of the day.
.
in the morning, and the morning, and the morning, and the morning, and the morning, and the
morning, and the morning, and the morning, and the morning, and the morning, and the
O Lord of mercy, save us who honor you.
By the ineffable will, born in the flesh is the fleshless one.
In body, now circumscribed, is the uncircumscribed,
immutably preserving both essences.
An origin receives he who in nature is unoriginate
and alone transcends time.
As an infant is perceived, he who transcends perfection.
or
Born in arms is he who bears the universe.
Therefore, as God, by his birth, he crowns those who have the honor of being his kin.
Whom we glorify with faith as we cry without ceasing.
O Lord of mercy, save us who honor you.
On December 28th, we commemorate the holy 20,000 who burned in Nicodemus.
media. On this day, we also commemorate the holy martyrs who were in the Senate, who fled from the
fire, died. Saint Indos died by drowning in the sea. Saints Gorgon and Peter died in the sea.
The holy martyr Zeno died by the sword. The holy martyr Mardonios died by fire. Saint Dorotheos,
the courtier, died by the sword. Saint Theophilus, the deacon, died by stoning.
Saint McDonough.
died by being burned in a pit.
Saint Glicarius, the priest, died by fire.
On this day, Saint Domna was cut by the sword
and died by fire.
The devout Saint Simon the Myrstreamer,
the founder of the holy monastery of Simonopetra
on Athos reposed in peace.
On this Sunday after Christmas,
we also commemorate the holy and righteous ancestors of God,
Joseph, the betrothed of Our Lady the Lord.
the Holy Theotokos, and Virgin Mary,
James, or Jacobos,
the brother of the Lord,
and David, the prophet and king.
By the intercessions of your saints, O God,
have mercy on us and save us. Amen.
Amen.
O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O Lord, O
God, good one,
humiliating
the faithful look
of the foe.
Blessed Lord,
who see all things
above all sin,
now raise us up,
us up, establish us,
your faithful
singers,
resolute and firm
upon the sure
base of faith.
Once was
up
prophet, have a
comb counted worthy,
passed all expression to see
Christ's birth depicted.
And he foretold
singing of mankind's
renewal. For a babe came from
a mountain, the pure virgin,
A young child the world
to renew all the peoples.
Amen.
Sunken in the waves of the sea's deepest waters,
the prophet Jonas implored you,
calm the tempest.
And I, O Christ,
punctured by the tyrant's arrow,
I call upon you,
from sloth now redeem me
Το πανάναχτος εξαφάλισαν τόπο,
απλή, απλή, απλή μέλοντος η κιτρωμένη,
παιδες τυράγον της θέων,
κομσαλγίαν, της η κατευθύρ,
άστε τον τόπες στόρτη,
Έχω σύνησε όλα σε προκυθώσει
We praise, bless, and worship the Lord, walking through fire unburned, the youths in the furnace, our types of the seal, virgin womb of the maiden.
when she gave birth past all nature to the Savior.
It was the same grace both from one.
from one wondrous power and raise the people to sing praise of the Master.
Σε παναπάβη και Σε την δόξα να αναπέμβομαι,
το Πατρί και το Υιό και το Υιό πνεύμα την Ήχεία
και εις τους αιώνας των αιωνών.
Αμήν.
Άσαν νοήεν έσαν το του Θήριον.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Let us pray to the Lord our God that we may be made worthy to hear the Holy Gospel.
Wisdom arise, let us hear the Holy Gospel. Peace be to you all.
The reading is from the Holy Gospel according to St. John.
little
be attentive.
Glory to you, O Lord. Glory to you.
At that time, Mary Magdalene came to the tomb early,
while it was still dark,
and saw that the stone had been taken away from the tomb.
So she ran and went to Simon Peter and the other disciple,
and the one whom Jesus loved, and said to them,
They have taken the Lord out of the tomb,
and we do not know where they have laid him.
Thank you.
Peter then came out with the other disciple and they went towards the tomb.
They both ran.
But the other disciple outran Peter and reached the tomb first and stooping to look in.
He saw the linen cloth laying there, but he did not go in.
Then Simon Peter came following him and went into the tomb.
He saw the linen cloth laying and the napkin which had been on his head not let
with the linen cloth, but rather rolled up in the place by itself.
Then the other disciple who reached the tomb first
also went in and his soul unbelieved.
For as yet they did not know the scripture
that he must rise from the dead.
Then the disciples went back into their home.
glory to you
having beheld the resurrection of christ let us worship the holy lord jesus the only sinless one
Your cross of Christ we venerate
and your holy resurrection we praise.
glorify. For you are our God. Apart from you we know no other. We call upon your name.
Come, all faithful, let us venerate the holy resurrection of Christ. For behold, through
the cross, joy has come to the whole world. Ever blessing, O Lord, let us praise his resurrection
for having endured the cross for us, he destroyed death by death.
Wash me thoroughly from my lawlessness and cleanse me from my sins.
Oh
Against you only have I sinned and done evil in your sight,
that you may be justified in your burns and overcome when you are judged.
You showed me the unknown and secret things of your wisdom.
You shall make me a joy and gladness.
My bones that were humbled shall greatly rejoice.
Turn your face from my sins and blot out all my transgressions.
Create in me a clean heart, O God, and renew a right spirit within me.
Me avaricis me apotu trotsopu su, ke to pnetman su to agionia dan Elisabewu.
Restore to me the joy of your salvation, and uphold me with your guiding spirit.
Deliver me from blood guiltiness, O God, the God of my salvation,
and my tongue shall greatly rejoice in your righteousness.
For if you desired sacrifice, I would give it.
You will not be pleased with all burnt offerings.
To God.
O Lord, in your good pleasure to Zion,
and let the walls of Jerusalem be built.
We offer you in San Christ our God,
as an offering of spiritual fragrances,
we receive it to the altar.
Send to us in the Trinity, praise the Holy Spirit.
And the star came and stood over the place
where the child was with Mary, his mother.
Then shall they offer young bolts on your altar,
and have mercy on me, O God.
Lord, Francis called himself
God Almighty, the others, all the ingredients of strength for us.
May the fall of you all and the Lord be moved.
Your glory has covered the heavens and the earth is filled with your blood.
Cover us and the shelter of your wings, right away from us,
with the forebring peace and our life.
Lord, you have mercy on us, your world, as a good and loving God, save us, so much.
For now and ever and to the ages of ages, Amen.
At the intercessions of the day of the Lord,
the sending forth and precious give us the spirit of the Lord,
Lord, and mercy of God,
God send the heavenly breath and nourish the whole world.
Lord God, Jesus Christ,
remember the fact of blessing and sacrifice us.
We will now bless this celebration,
exceding to your altar of all the heavens,
as a good and loving God.
Remember those who have offered his gifts
and those for whom they were offered in whole life,
blameless in the performance of the world of ministries.
For blessed and blessed is glorified in your holy,
majestic name of the Father,
Son, and Spirit, now and forever,
and ever, amen.
Holy God, Father, eternal,
holy, mighty Son,
for your holy, mighty Son,
for your holy, mighty Son, for your holy, mighty Son,
for your holy, mighty Son, for your holy,
glory to you.
You will go to the Father, the Son, and the Holy Spirit, now and the Father, and the Holy Spirit. Amen.
Lord, have mercy, Lord, have mercy, Lord, have mercy.
May Christ our God, who was born in the cave and rose from the dead,
through the prayers of His most pure Holy Mother, our Father, and the saints,
show us the most beautiful person of the temple, all the saints have mercy on us and save us for His good.
May we have mercy on us and save us for His good.
So...
Through the mercies of your only
O Michael and Lady Theotokos of the Virgin Mary
The power of the precious and life-giving cross
The protection of the honorable heavenly bodiless powers
The supplication of the honorable glorious prophet
And foran of John the Baptist
The holy, glorious and praiseworthy apostles
Our Father among the saints
the great
hierarchies
and ecumenical teachers, Basil the Great, Gregory the Theologian,
and John Chrysostom, Athanasius, Sirius, John Merciful,
Patricks of Alexandria, Nicholas, Bishop of Myra,
Spirit-owned Bishop of Demetrius, Nectarius of Pentapolis,
the Wonder Workers, the Holy Glorious Great Martyrs,
George the Triumphant, Demetrius, the Mysterious Mother,
Theodore the Soldier, and Theodore the General,
Minas the Wonder Worker, Harambos, and Rephterios,
the Hayro Mothers
the holy, glorious, and victorious martyrs,
the glorious, great martyr, and laudable Ephemia,
the holy, glorious martyrs,
Thecla Barvara, Anastasia, Katerine Kiryaki,
Fotini Marina, Paraskevi, and Irene,
our venerable and God-bearing fathers,
the holy and righteous ancestors of Lord Joachim and Anna,
of the holy, righteous Joseph, betrothed David, the king,
and James, the brother of the Lord,
whose memory
we observe and all your saints.
We beseech you only, merciful Lord.
Hear our sinners who pray to you and have mercy on all.
Lord, have mercy. Lord, have mercy. Lord, have mercy.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Θεοτόκον και μητέρα του φωτός, εν ύμνης τιμών τες μεγαλύνομαι.
Ω, Ανανέ.
Μεγαλύτη, πληκτή μου, τωσκύριου, εγχασμία σπέτω στους πνεύμασους,
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O
you call me
blessed
greater in honor
than the cherubim
and in glory
greater beyond
than the seraphim
you without
corruption
gave birth to call the word
and are truly
failed the whole coast
you do we magnify
um
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
He has shown strength with his arm, he has scattered the proud
in the imagination of their hearts.
Greater in honor than the cherubim,
in London, Wyoming, greater than the world.
oh
This is Zogadam, friend of mine.
He has helped his servant Israel in remembrance of his mercy.
With Gabriel we sing your praise.
With shepherds we give glory as we cry.
Mother of God, intercede with him.
Who was incarnate of you.
And we may be saved
I have begotten you from the womb before the morning star
The Lord swore and will not repent
The Father was well pleased
The Logos became flesh
And the Virgin gave birth to him
Who became a man
A star reveals him
Magi bow.
in worship shepherds marvel and creation rejoices
Maia
Glory to the Father and the Son.
and the Holy Spirit.
Blood and fire
and vapor of smoke.
Oh
These are the potions that joked for sun on the earth.
The blood.
is the incarnation of Christ.
The fire.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
Bye.
of smoke is the Holy Spirit.
Oh
Is
And
The world with sweet fragrance
Grave
the mystery of your incarnation.
Oh, Lord, Lord.
in the
Lord.
Both now and ever
and to the ages of ages.
Amen.
You are highly blessed
all the
virgin mother of God,
for through him who was incarnate from you,
hell has been taken captive.
Adam recalled the curse slain.
He said, free death has been put to death,
and we have been given life.
Therefore with hymns we cry out,
Blessed are you, God.
Christ our God, who have been thus well pleased, glory to you.
We praise you.
We bless you, we worship you, we glorify you.
We give thanks to you for your great glory.
O Lord God, Lamb of God, Son of the Father,
who take away the sin of the world,
have mercy on us, you who take away the sin of the world.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Ετύδιο μετά υπέρ των αδελφών ημών, των ιερών, ηραμανάχων, ηρωδιακών, και μοναχών και πάσης της εν Χριστώ ημών αδελφότητος.
Κύριε Λέισον, Κύριε Λέισον, Κύριε Λέισον.
Ετύδιο μετά υπέρ ελεύου ζωής, ηλίνης, ηγείας, οτιδείας, επισκέψεως, συγχωρήσεως και αφέσεως των αμαρτιών των δούλων του Θεού,
πάντων των ευσεβών και οθοδόξων χριστιανών, των κατοικούντων και παρεπιτιμούντων,
εν την πολιτάθη των ενωλητών επιτρόφων συνδρομητών και αφαιρέτων του Αγίου Ναουτού του.
Κύριε Ρέισον, Κύριε Ρέισον.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Αντιλαβού στους ελεήσεων, Κύριε φύλαξον ημάς ο Θεός της ηχάρητη, Κύριε Ελεήσεων, την ημέρα πάσα, τελείαν, Αγία Νερυνικήν και Αναμάρτητον, παρά του Κύριου της Σώμας, Κύριε.
Look upon the humble and who with all deceiving eye I do behold all creation.
To you have we bowed the neck of our souls and bodies and implored you,
holy of holies, stretch forth your invisible hand from your early building place
and bless us all.
And if in any way we have sinned, either willingly or intentionally,
pardon us as much as you are good and love humankind,
granting us your good things in this age and years to come,
eternal life.
For your cities to show mercy and to save our Christ,
I guarantee you we give glory, Father, Son, and Holy Spirit,
now and forever in the ages of ages, amen.
wisdom
Blessed are you, Christ our God, always, now, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and forever, and
the holy glorious and praiseworthy apostles of our holy righteous ancestors of the Lord,
the Lord, the Lord, the Lord, the Lord, the Lord, the Lord, the Lord, the Lord, the Lord, the Lord,
of Saint Joseph, Saint David, the King, and of all the saints whose memory we celebrate today,
and of all your saints, have mercy on us and save us for his good and loves humankind.
Through the prayers of our holy fathers, Lord Jesus Christ, our God, have mercy on us and save us. Amen.
Let us sing to him who rose from the tomb, the author of our life.
for the
Destroying death by death,
He has given us the victory
and His great mercy.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Kyrie Eleison
For our country, for the president, all in public service, let us pray to the Lord.
For this city and every city and land and the faithful who live in them, let us pray to the Lord.
For favorable weather, for the abundance of the fruits of the earth and for peaceful times, let us pray to the Lord.
Lord, have mercy.
For the sick, the suffering, the captives, and their salvation, let us pray to the Lord.
Thank you.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
For to you belong all glory and worship to the Father and the Son and the Holy Spirit, now and forever and to the ages of ages.
Amen.
I will give thanks to you, O Lord, with my whole heart. I will tell of all your wondrous things.
Lord our God, whose dominion is incomparable and glory incomprehensible,
whose mercy is immeasurable enough,
for mankind and in the world.
Lord, look upon us
and upon this holy house
in your loving kindness
and grant to us
and to those who pray with us
their honor and mercy and compassion.
Through the intercessions
of the Theotokos
Savior, save us.
Excellency in manna is one
of the lima bar food
That's
Thanksgiving and majesty are his work,
and his righteousness continues unto ages of ages.
Through the intercessions of the Theotokos,
Savior, save us.
Foxa Patrice
Again and again in peace let us pray to the Lord.
Oh, my God.
Help us, save us, have mercy on us, and protect us, O God, by your grace.
Commemorating our most holy, pure, blessed, and glorious Lady, the Theotokos,
and our Virgin Mary, with all the saints,
let us command ourselves and one another and our whole life to Christ our God.
For yours is a
dominion and yours is the kingdom and the power and the glory of the father and the son and
holy spirit now and forever and to the ages of ages
lord our god savior people bless our inheritance protect the fullness of your church sanctify
your soul out to be here your house glorify the man by your divine part forsake us not
God, You have granted us to offer this common praise in You, Son, and I promise unto You
three green your name your grander requests fulfill our lord the petitions of your servants
as may be of benefit to them granting us in the present nationals of your future
in the age to come return in life
this seed shall be mighty on earth save us oh son of god who are born of a virgin
as we sing to you.
Alleluia.
Glory and riches shall be in his house,
and his righteousness continues unto ages of ages.
So, sonima si etheu,
o ec parthenon te chris,
salontasi alleluia.
Oh
Αμήν.
Σταυρωθείς σε Χριστέ ο Θεός, θάνατο, θάνατον πατήσας
Ίσον της Αγίας Τριάδος, συνδοξαζόμενος το Πατρί και το Αγίο Πνεύματι σώσον ημάς
Είδα.
Thank you.
Μετά πάντων των Αγίων μνημονεύσανται σε αυτούς
και αλλήλους και πάσαν την ζωήν ημών
Χριστό το Θεό παραθώ μεθά
Ση Κύριε
Ό,τι αγαθός και φιλάνθρωπος Θεός υπάρχει
και εσύ την δόξαν αναπέμπομεν το πατρί και το Υιό
και το Υιό πνεύματι την Κυαή
και έστω σε όλα όσα